Guide to the Hoover Institution Archives Motion Picture Films
Hoover Institution Archives
- Winbigler (H. Donald) motion picture film collection, 1942-1943; http://www.oac.cdlib.org/findaid/ark:/13030/kt338nf002 (Box 87065: Film Shelf)
  Films are newsreels depicting the American invasion of North Africa in 1942, and the capture of Tarawa by American forces in 1943. (2 16mm films)
- Yourieff (Alexandra Andreevna Voronine) papers, undated; http://www.oac.cdlib.org/findaid/ark:/13030/kt6q2nd66g (Box 2003C45: Film Shelf)
  The collection includes an Unidentified. motion picture. (1 8mm films)
- Zhang (Shuqi) papers, undated; http://www.oac.cdlib.org/findaid/ark:/13030/kt9g503866 (Box 98028: Film Shelf)
  The films in the collection show Professor Zhang Shuqi painting. (2 16mm films)
  "Harmon Foundation and China Institute in America motion picture film: Out of a Chinese painting brush: Professor Chang Shu-Chi shows his masterful skill." Use copy reference number: 98028_f_0000779.
  "Royal Ontario Museum of Archaeology motion picture film: a Chinese artist: the method and technique of Chang Shu-chi professor of fine arts in the National Central University of China." Use copy reference number: 98028_f_0000780.